<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asgard PvP Realm on AsgardPvP</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asgard PvP Realm on AsgardPvP</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Progon &amp; Holy</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Breakpoints [FBR / FHR / FCR / FRW / IAS]</title>
      <link>/guides/bp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/bp/</guid>
      <description>In Diablo 2, a second is divided into 25 frames. As a result, every action (animation) is measured in these frames. By reaching certain breakpoints, you increase the speed of the animations.  Recommended breakpoints will be marked red.  It is worth mentioning that further suggestions are rather PvP-oriented, yet they are pretty similar to PvE ones.  FBR   FBR stands for Faster Block Rate. When you get hit with physical damage, you have a chance to block it (if you have a shield).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C/T Trick [CT]</title>
      <link>/guides/ct/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/ct/</guid>
      <description>The name of the C/T Trick comes from the default binds that are used for this technique.  C — Character Screen  T— Skill Tree  Of course, these binds should be changed. Personally, I have them as follows: &#34;A&#34; — CS, S — ST, but when playing Hdin I am lack available binds, so I had to bind Fanaticism on &#34;T&#34;, which is not very convenient. One of my friend&#39;s binds are as follows: &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contacts</title>
      <link>/contacts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contacts/</guid>
      <description> General:   Jsp
Skype
Discord: t4wE#5142
E-mail
Facebook
Vk  Streams:   Twitch
Youtube
Goodgame  Skype and Discord conversations where you can find an opponent for duels:   Skype
Discord </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create account</title>
      <link>/create-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/create-account/</guid>
      <description>  Remember, that your password should be a maximum of 12 symbols long!
Sometimes there is a bug when the password you chose will appear incorrect when trying to enter it in the game (usually happens when your password contains symbols other than Latin letters or numbers).
Contact us and we will fix it.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cube recipes</title>
      <link>/cube-recipes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cube-recipes/</guid>
      <description>First of all, remember that there are in-game accounts that contain the most popular items:  *items (has most hard-to-roll rares/crafts bases etc.) *chars (has ready-to-go geared builds)   All items respawn every 2 hours so don&#39;t be shy to take anything you want from those accounts. You can as well simply copy chars from *chars account by dropping all they got on the ground and then picking it all up with your character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desynch Bug [Jodering]</title>
      <link>/guides/desynch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/desynch/</guid>
      <description>Due to lack of skill, some players decided to ease the usage of buttons on their keyboard and created their own playstyle - jodering. It&#39;s simply desynching around all the map and spamming invisible Hammers, hoping some newbie will fly into them. They even examined the best ways to make desynch better (bumping into holes, etc.). So they created an illusion of skill in desynch usage. Like you must be experienced, so you can master this &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diablo 2 PvP/Duels #guidlines for a PvP beginner</title>
      <link>/guides/pvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/pvp/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my dear friend! This article is made for all those who have just started their journey as a PvP player in Diablo 2. I will try to show the bigger picture, give you some tips (to guide you on the right path, so to say) and motivate.  Diablo 2 — is an iconic Hack&#39;n&#39;Slash game of all time. This game was indeed done wisely and thoughtfully. It was made from the heart and was intended for ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FPK</title>
      <link>/fpk-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fpk-rules/</guid>
      <description>FPK - are certain dueling rules where four characters (Druid, Necromancer, Barbarian, Assassin) play by them.  These FPK rules are made and adjusted specifically for Asgard PvP Realm. If the game has an &#34;fpk&#34; prefix (e.g.&#34;fpk duels&#34;), then don&#39;t be a jerk and obey them - otherwise, you might be kicked out of the game by one of the moderators. Continuous disobeying might lead to a temp/perm ban.  General rules   The duel starts once everybody said &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GM Rules</title>
      <link>/gm-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gm-rules/</guid>
      <description>GM - are certain dueling rules, most popular and fair ones.  These GM rules are made and adjusted specifically for Asgard PvP Realm. If the game has a &#34;gm&#34; prefix (e.g.&#34; gm duels&#34;), then don&#39;t be a jerk and obey them - otherwise, you might be kicked out of the game by one of the moderators. Continuous disobeying might lead to a temp/perm ban.  General rules   The duel starts once everybody said &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guides</title>
      <link>/guides/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/</guid>
      <description> List of guides:   Diablo 2 PvP/Duels #guidlines for a PvP beginner IBS [Train] Swirls [Smite/Shock Wave] Skill Bug [SB] Desynch Bug [Jodering] C/T Trick [CT] WSM Bug [+Auto WSM] Strength Bug [Str Bug] Tank Trick [TT] WSG [Weapon Switch Glitch] Stomping [Namelock, Lock (Stomp), Chainlock, Chain] Breakpoints [FBR / FHR / FCR / FRW / IAS] What server to pick in 2k21 Truth about PvP on PG </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to connect</title>
      <link>/how-to-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-connect/</guid>
      <description>Step 1   Install Diablo II and Lord of Destruction Expansion.  Step 2   Our server requires version 1.14d. If you already have 1.14d, then just skip further to step 3. If you have version 1.13d or less - you got two options:   Option #1   Our server has an automatic update till version 1.14d. So you can just download our reg file.  Add the server&#39;s info to the registry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBS [Train]</title>
      <link>/guides/ibs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/ibs/</guid>
      <description>The Train is a Necromancer&#39;s trick, flying in one line train of Bone Spirits. It is a very simple trick. We hold the Bone Spirit skill in any of the corners of the screen. After five casts of Spirits, we switch to TP and immediately back to Bone Spirit. The cursor does not move.   After 3 packs there will be about 15 Spirits which is about 75 k magic damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mod info</title>
      <link>/mod-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mod-info/</guid>
      <description>Pay attention!  Normal&#39;s penalties are the same as in Hell (-100 all res). However, they aren&#39;t shown correctly (visual bug), so you need to count them manually.  To avoid this you can download a mini-mod - watch the bottom of this page  Ladder features legit items only.
Non-Ladder features bugged items, hybrid runewords, 08 items.  Our server also features Low-Level Dueling (30 lvl). If you want to make an lld character — contact one of the moderators in-game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skill Bug[SB]</title>
      <link>/guides/sb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/sb/</guid>
      <description>The thing with this trick is a visual display of one skill, while you are actually using another.   In this case, Sorc is actually using Inferno, but Frozen Orb is displayed instead with FPA (Frames Per Attack) of Inferno. When performing Skill Bug all characters (except Paladin and Barbarian) do it while standing in one spot.  How does that help us in PvP, since it is just a &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stomping [Namelock, Lock (Stomp), Chainlock, Chain]</title>
      <link>/guides/stomp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/stomp/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s worth mentioning that if you play in a windowed mode (&#34;-w&#34; in the shortcut properties), you should install the Cursor Locker. Otherwise, your cursor will constantly fly out of the window and your play will simply be awful. So if you want to learn how to duel in Diablo 2 - make sure you download, install, and use it.  Namelock   Let&#39;s start with simple techniques. The thing with Namelock is to quickly and precisely aim at your opponent&#39;s nickname.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Strength Bug [Str Bug]</title>
      <link>/guides/str/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/str/</guid>
      <description>Prologue:  When Expansion Set &#34;Lord of Destruction&#34; was not yet released, the game looked a little different. There was only known to you now as &#34;classic&#34;. The fifth Act didn&#39;t exist, there were no charms, no runes.  Idea   During the game, the server sends information to your game client (and all other users connected to this game) telling what is happening.  For example:  Situation No.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swirls [Smite/Shock Wave]</title>
      <link>/guides/swirls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/swirls/</guid>
      <description>The effect of birds above your head (aka ~Swirls~) which is well-known from Assassin’s Mind Blast also procs from Smite and Shock Wave. The thing about these birds is that until they are circling over your head — any attack with any damage triggers Faster Hit Recovery animation. If not swirled, FHR will only take place when you get damage that takes away at least 1/16 of your hp in a single hit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tank Trick [TT]</title>
      <link>/guides/tt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/tt/</guid>
      <description>You need to know what WSG is before reading this.  So, WSG is a technique for &#34;breaking&#34; FHR animation and increasing desynchronization. But few people know that this technique can be used not only when running, but when you teleport and even attack. No special complications/differences from WSG.  Tank Trick while teleport will help you avoid the Leap of Barb:   Often you&#39;ll be caught for double or even triple Leap   *4th second of the video  In case you won&#39;t Tank Trick you can be double Leaped and you will be separated from your stack and most likely die from Barb&#39;s stomp&amp;gt;WW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traps IAS Calculator</title>
      <link>/ias/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ias/</guid>
      <description>td:hover,th:hover {background-color: inherit;}td,th {border: 1px solid grey;text-align: center;padding: 0px;margin: 0px;}Mirror of &amp;amp; Credits goes to &#34;xepolite.technocow.nl&#34; Assa Trap Laying Speed CalculatorXepolite&#39;s shithole!&#34;Where Assassins take a dump&#34;IAS CalculatorHelm0%15%30%35%45%Amu0%20%Primary SlotAncient AxeAncient SwordArbalestArchon StaffAtaghanAxeBalanced AxeBalanced KnifeBalistaBalrog BladeBalrog SpearBarbed ClubBardicheBastard SwordBattle AxeBattle CestusBattle DartBattle HammerBattle ScytheBattle StaffBattle SwordBearded AxeBec-de-CorbinBerserker AxeBillBladeBlade BowBlade TalonsBone KnifeBone WandBrandistockBroad AxeBroad SwordBurnt WandCaduceusCedar BowCedar StaffCestusChampion AxeChampion SwordChu-Ko-NuCinquedeasClawsClaymoreCleaverClubColossus SwordColossus BladeColossus CrossbowColossus VoulgeComposite BowConquest SwordCrossbowCrowbillCrusader BowCryptic AxeCryptic SwordCrystal SwordCudgelCutlassDacian FalxDaggerDecapitatorDemon CrossbowDemon HeartDevil StarDiamond BowDimensional BladeDimensional ShardDirkDivine ScepterDouble AxeDouble BowEdge BowElder StaffElegant BladeEspandonEttin AxeExecutioner SwordFalcataFalchionFanged KnifeFasciaFeral AxeFeral ClawsFlailFlambergeFlanged MaceFlying AxeFlying KnifeFranciscaFuscinaGhost GlaiveGhost SpearGhost WandGiant AxeGiant SwordGiant ThresherGladiusGlaiveGlorious AxeGnarled StaffGorgon CrossbowGothic AxeGothic BowGothic StaffGothic SwordGrand Matron BowGrand ScepterGrave WandGreat AxeGreat BowGreat MaulGreat PilumGreat PoleaxeGreat SwordGreater ClawsGreater TalonsGrim ScytheGrim WandHalberdHand AxeHand ScytheHarpoonHatchetHatchet HandsHeavy CrossbowHighland BladeHoly Water SprinklerHunter&#39;s BowHurlbatHydra BowHydra EdgeHyperion JavelinHyperion SpearJagged StarJared&#39;s StoneJavelinJo StaffKatarKnoutKrisLanceLarge AxeLarge Siege BowLegend SpikeLegend SwordLegendary MalletLich WandLight CrossbowLochaber AxeLong Battle BowLong BowLong StaffLong SwordLong War BowMaceMancatcherMartel de FerMaulMighty ScepterMilitary AxeMilitary PickMithril PointMorning StarMythical SwordNagaOgre AxeOgre MaulPartizanPellet BowPetrified WandPhase BladePikePilumPoignardPoleaxePolished WandQuarterstaffQuhabRazor BowReflex BowReinforced MaceRepeating CrossbowRondelRune BowRune ScepterRune StaffRune SwordRunic TalonsSabreSacred GlobeScepterScimitarScissors KatarScissors QuhabScissors SuwayyahScourgeScytheSeraph RodShadow BowShamshirShillelaghShort Battle BowShort BowShort Siege BowShort SpearShort StaffShort SwordShort War BowSiege CrossbowSilver Edged AxeSimbilanSmall CrescentSpearSpetumSpiculumSpider BowSpiked ClubStag BowStalagmiteStilettoStygian PikeStygian PilumSuwayyahTabarThresherThrowing AxeThrowing KnifeThrowing SpearThunder MaulTomahawkTomb WandTridentTruncheonTulwarTusk SwordTwin AxeTwo-Handed SwordTyrant ClubUnearthed WandVoulgeWalking StickWandWar AxeWar ClubWar DartWar FistWar ForkWar HammerWar JavelinWar PikeWar ScepterWar ScytheWar SpearWar SpikeWar StaffWar SwordWard BowWinged AxeWinged HarpoonWinged KnifeWrist BladeWrist SpikeWrist SwordYariYew WandZweihander</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truth about PvP on PG</title>
      <link>/guides/pg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/pg/</guid>
      <description> This article explains, how poor are the conditions for dueling on the Russian Playground.ru server. Won&#39;t be interesting for EU guys, so just forget it ;) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What server to pick in 2k21</title>
      <link>/guides/server/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/server/</guid>
      <description>I will try to make a little server classification here. I will point out the pros and cons of every single one so it will be up to you to pick which one to play on.  All servers can be divided into:   Official  Unofficial   Official   These are well-known to you Europe/US West/US East/Asia. These are official servers. Ya need to buy a CD-Key to play here for two games: D2 и D2: LoD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WSG [Weapon Switch Glitch]</title>
      <link>/guides/wsg/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/wsg/</guid>
      <description>WSG is a simple basic technique in PvP. The essence of the trick lies in the constant switching of weapons while running.  What you should know about swapping:  Swapping breaks FHR animation Swapping increases desynchronization   FHR   So the animation of Faster Hit Recovery, depending on the class lasts somewhere between 4 and 7 frames. If you will swap weapons during this animation, the animation of FHR will end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WSM Bug [&#43;Auto WSM]</title>
      <link>/guides/wsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:20:47 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/guides/wsm/</guid>
      <description>When I was digging for this info, this site helped me a lot. There&#39;s a lot of text there, so I&#39;m going to simplify it a little.  So, to avoid further misunderstanding:  (c) all right reserved Xepolite&#39;s shithole!  WSM Bug is intended to decrease the requirement of IAS to reach a 9-frame trap laying breakpoint without* using BoS.  *Against chars that deal physical damage, we will use Fade, because it gives us DR that can&#39;t be taken from other items (102 fcr build).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
